Finding Aid for the Ayres & Fiege Architectural Drawings LSC.0115
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Residential projects., 1939-1970
  - Subseries C: Additions and renovations., 1939-1968.; 30 map folders
    - (2 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 204)
      - R. Nelson residence., 1961.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 61-29. Addition to R. Nelson residence
        17180 Rayen St. Northridge, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section and elevation.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. Nelson.
      - Prinzmetal residence., 1961.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 61-32. Addition to Prinzmetal residence
        645 Comstock Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Prinzmetal.
      - Crossen residence., 1961.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 61-37. Addition to Crossen residence
        3612 Woodhill Canyon Rd. Studio City, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Frank Crossen.
      - Breakstone residence., 1961.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 61-42. Addition to Breakstone residence
        12634 Albers, North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevation and details.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. G. Breakstone.
      - Block residence., 1961.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 61-43. Remodeling of Block residence
        800 Warner Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevation and detail.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Block.
      - Gobbell residence., 1961.; 6.; 1 item.
        Job Number 61-46. Addition to Gobbell residence
        5236 Bianca Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Dr. W. M. Gobbell.
      - Marks residence., 1961.; 7.; 1 item.
        Job Number 61-48. Addition to Marks residence
        12943 Galewood, Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Larry Marks.
    - (1 of 2)., 1962 (Folder 205)
      - Squeo residence., 1962.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 62-1. Addition to Squeo residence
        8833 Amboy St. Sun Valley, CA.
        Owner: Nickolas Squeo.
      - MacDougall residence., 1962.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 62-4. Remodeling of MacDougall residence
        141 South Windsor, Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans and interior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Allan MacDuogall Jr.
      - Tryer residence., 1962.; 3.; 5 items.
        Job Number 62-12. Remodeling of Tryer residence
        5320 Wortser Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H. L. Tryer.
      - Lavet residence., 1962.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 62-13. Alterations and additions to Lavet residence
        11943 Briarvale Ln. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Norman Lavet.
      - Knoll residence., 1962.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 62-14. Addition to Knoll residence
        7753 Greenbush Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Bill Knoll.
    - (2 of 2)., 1962 (Folder 206)
      - McNally residence., 1962.; 1.; 1 item.
        Job Number 62-18. Addition to McNally residence
        6224 Orion St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, details and elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. S. McNally.
      - Bader residence., 1962.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 62-20. Alterations and additions to Bader residence
        4625 Ledge Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawing: plans
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F. J. Bader.
      - Drueal residence., 1962.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 62-21. Alterations and additions to Drueal residence
        8814 Evanview, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Hugo Drueal.
      - Laird residence., 1962.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 62-22. Alterations and additions to Laird residence
        15943 Valley Vista, Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Robert S. Laird.
    - ., 1963-1964 (Folder 207)
      - Hart residence., 1963.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 63-16. Alterations and additions to Hart residence
        3619 Crownridge Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Dick Hart.
      - Binder residence., 1963.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 63-27. Addition to Binder residence
        5447 Onacrest Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Don Binder.
      - Levine residence., 1963.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 63-28. Tea House for Levine residence
        11401 Dona Evita Dr. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jack Levine.
      - Scharf residence., 1964.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 64-12. Alterations and additions to Scharf residence
        3372 Longridge Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Larry Scharf.
      - Buckley residence., 1964.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 64-23. Alterations and additions to Buckley residence
        2015 Irvine Ave. Costa Mesa, CA.
        Owner: Dr. Buckley.
    - ., 1965-1967 (Folder 208)
      - R. X. Nelson residence., 1965.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 65-1. Addition to R. X. Nelson residence
        5811 Round Meadow Rd. Hidden Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. X. Nelson.
      - Killingworth residence., 1965.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 65-18. Addition to Killingworth residence
        8020 Hinds Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. G. and B. Killingworth.
      - Dooley residence., 1966.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 66-9. Addition to Dooley residence
        15204 Sutton St. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Copy of drawings: plans, sections, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: C. T. Dooley.
      - Estrada residence., 1967.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 67-18. Addition to Estrada residence
        16648 Bryant St. Sepulveda, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Rual Estrada.
    - (1 of 3)., 1968 (Folder 209)
      - 1968--Blocker., 13 items.
        Job Number 68-1. Remodeling and additions to Blocker residence
        555 Muirfield Rd. Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Dan Blocker.
    - (2 of 3)., 1968 (Folder 210)
      - 1968--Blocker., 20 items.
        Copy of drawings: plans, sections, details, perspectives, interior and exterior elevations.
    - (3 of 3)., 1968 (Folder 211)
      - 1968--Blocker., CA. 25 items.
        Drawings on trace paper: details, elevations and perspectives.
    - ., 1968 (Folder 212)
      - Green residence., 1968.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 68-7. Additions to Green residence
        2090 Mandeville Canyon Rd. Pacific Palisades, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Lorne Green.
      - Eller residence., 1968.; 2.; 10 items.
        Loggia addition to Eller residence
        10370 Glenbarr Ave. W. Los Angeles, CA.
        Drawings on trace: plan and perspectives.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jay Eller.
  - Subseries D: Model and tract homes., 1947-1964.; 30 map folders
    Designs for real estate developers, often duplicated in different locations (or customized for private clients).
    - Miscellaneous. (Folder 213)
      - "Living in San Fernando Valley"., no date.; 1.; 1 item.
        "Living in San Fernando Valley"
        Original Poster: plan, interior and exterior views.
      - G. I. House., no date.; 2.; 1 item.
        G. I. House
      - Model Homes., no date.; 3.; 1 item.
        Model Homes- no specified date or developer
        Original drawings: perspective for "The America".
    - ., 1947-1948 (Folder 214)
      - Residence for M and M building corp., 1947.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 603-c. Residence for M and M building corp.
        Original drawings: plans, section, elevations.
        Owner: M and M Building Corp.
      - Noble & Olsen., 1948.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 708. Residence for Noble & Olsen
        4217 Havenhurst Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Noble & Olsen Inc.
      - Noble & Olsen., 1948.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 711. Residence for Noble & Olsen
        4319 Havenhurst Ave. Encino, CA.
      - Mr. & Mrs. Bender., 1948.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 722. Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Bender
        13980 Davana Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jack Bender.
      - Sherwood Construction Co., 1948.; 5.; 5 items.
        Job Number 723. Residence for Sherwood Construction Co.
        15655 Woodvale Rd. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Sherwood Construction Co.
    - ., 1949-1950 (Folder 215)
      - Harry Hart., 1949.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 750. Residences for Harry Hart, builder
        Jellico St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawing and copies: plot and roof plans.
        Owner: Harry Hart, builder.
      - Desert Home, Yucca Estates., 1949.; 2.; 13 items.
        Job Number 765. Desert Home, Yucca Estates
        Lakota Rd. Apple Valley, Yucca Estates, CA.
      - Hart Construction Co., 1950.; 3.; 1 item.
        Residence for Hart Construction Co.
        Original drawings: plans and elevation.
      - Swenson & Groff., 1950.; 4.; 6 items.
        Job Number 848. House "C" for Swenson & Groff
        Owner: David Swenson & Dr. A. S. Abdun-Mur.
    - (1 of 3)., 1951 (Folder 216)
      - Jackbilt., 1950.; 1.; 10 items.
        Job Number 861. Residence & garage for Jackbilt
        2404 Via Rivera, Palos Verdes Estates, CA.
        Owner: Jackbilt Inc.
      - Sherman Woods., 1951.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 869. Sherman Woods residence
        15824 Woodvale Rd. Sherman Woods, CA.
        Owner: McDonald Co.
      - Hugo Swanson., 1951.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 871. "The Country Gentleman" for Hugo Swanson
        23399 Leonara, Woodland Hills, CA.
        Owner: Hugo Swanson.
      - Martson Residence., 1951?; 4.; 6 items.
        Job Number 884. Martson Residence, Marston & Grimes revised car port.
        Owner: Martson.
    - (2 of 3)., 1951 (Folder 217)
      - Burroughs Inc.., 1951.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 890. Residence for Burroughs Inc.
        Burbank Blvd. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Owner: Edgar Rice Burroughs Inc.
      - Sherwood Construction Co., 1951.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 902. Residence for Sherwood Construction Co.
      - Martson & Grimes., 1951.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 906. Residence for Martson & Grimes
        Owner: Martson & Grimes Inc. (Merle L. & Claire E. Strayer).
      - Ranch House for L. A. Lefevre & Sons., 1951.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 907. Ranch House for L. A. Lefevre & Sons
        Owner: Lefevre & Sons Inc.
      - Martson & Grimes., 1951.; 5.; 7 items.
        Job Number 908. "Highland Cottage" for Martson & Grimes
        Roscomare Rd. Bel Air Highlands, CA.
        Owner: Martson & Grimes Inc.
    - (3 of 3)., 1951 (Folder 218)
      - E. Steinkamp., 1951?; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 916, 928 930. E. Steinkamp - 75' lot
        Owner: E. Steinkamp Inc.
      - E. Steinkamp., 1951.; 2.; 13 items.
        Job Number 917. "The Island View" for E. Steinkamp
        Linda Flora Rd. Bel Air Highlands, CA.
        Drawing of alteration to plan 917 for Mr. Pecaro (project 55-29).
      - E. Steinkamp., 1951.; 3.; 11 items.
        Copy of drawings: plans, sections, details, interior and exterior elevations.
      - Martson & Grimes., 1951.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 931. "Trails End" for Martson & Grimes
        4610 Lindley Ave. Encino, CA.
        Copy of drawings: plans, sections, details and elevations.
    - (1 of 2)., 1952 (Folder 219)
      - E. Steinkamp., 1952.; 1.; 7 items.
        Job Number 928. "Dutch Haven" for E. Steinkamp.
        2339 Stradella Rd. Bel Air Highlands, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, section, interior and exterior elevations.
        Includes plan for Patty Residence (986).
      - Sherwood Co., 1952.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 969. "Little-Bit of Old England" for the Sherwood Co.
        McCormick St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: The Sherwood Co.
      - Martson & Grimes., 1952.; 3.; 5 items.
        Job Number 972. Residence for Martson & Grimes
    - (2 of 2)., 1952 (Folder 220)
      - Martson & Grimes., 1952.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 977. "Bel-View" for Martson & Grimes
        2246 Stradella Rd. Bel-Air.
      - Encino Estates., 1952.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 980. "Villacino" for Encino Estates
        Owner: Encino Estates- Earl L. White & Sons (Isle Inc.).
      - Martson & Grimes., 1952.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 981, 53-14. Residence for Martson & Grimes
        Drawing of alteration to plan 981 for Mr. Wilson (project 53-14).
    - (1 of 2)., 1953 (Folder 221)
      - Martson & Grimes., 1953.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 985. Residence for Martson & Grimes
      - Martson & Grimes., 1953.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 53-1. "Capri" for Martson & Grimes
        2261 Stradella Rd. Bel Air Highlands, CA.
      - Sherwood Construction Co., 1953.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-6. Residence for Sherwood Construction Co.
        Weddington St. Van Nuys, CA.
      - Martson & Grimes., 1953.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 53-16. "Globe Trotter" for Martson & Grimes
    - (2 of 2)., 1953 (Folder 222)
      - L.A. Lefevre & Sons., 1953.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 53-17. Residence for L.A. Lefevre & Sons
        Cassandra St. Tarzana, CA.
      - L.A. Lefevre & Sons., 1953.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-28. Model home for L.A. Lefevre & Sons
        18607 Cassandra St. Tarzana, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, details and elevations.
      - Model homes & alternations., 1953.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-34, 53-61. Model homes & alternations
        Includes a note saying "started for Martson- may be used any other way".
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R.D.Knoblauch, Mr. & Mrs. Ed. R. Myers.
      - Encino Estates., 1953.; 4.; 7 items.
        Job Number 53-46. Model home #2 for Encino Estates
        4049 Hayvenhurst, Encino, CA.
        Owner: Encino Estates- Earl L. White & sons.
    - (1 of 3)., 1954 (Folder 223)
      - Pan Pacific Aud., 1954.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 54-8. Remodel of exhibit house- home show, Pan Pacific Aud.
        Owner: Remodeling Contractors Association.
      - Hart Construction Co.., 1954.; 2.; 20 items.
        Job Numbers 54-31, 32, 33, 34. Tract No. 18081 for Hart Construction Co.
        Puente, Los Angeles County.
        Owner: Hart Construction Co.
    - (2 of 3)., 1954 (Folder 224)
      - Davana Terrace development., 1954-1955.; 20 items.
        Job Number 54-44. Davana Terrace development
        13967 Davana Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Sally Watkins (Dec. 1954) and Leon B. Traub (Feb. 1955).
    - (3 of 3)., 1954 (Folder 225)
      - Carfco Corp., 1954.; 11 items.
        Job Number 54-52. Tract No. 15275 for Carfco Corp.
        32 homes. San Fernando Mission Blvd.
        Owner: Carfco Corp.
    - (1 of 4)., 1955 (Folder 226)
      - Robin Aire Development Co., 1955.; 23 items.
        Job Numbers 55- 11, 28, 30, 46, 50, 51 55. "Anniversary Home" for Robin Aire Development Co. and related work (1 of 2)
        Owner: Robin Aire Development Co.
    - (2 of 4)., 1955 (Folder 227)
      - Robin Aire Development Co., 1955-57.; 16 items.
        Job Numbers 55- 61, 72, 57-40. "Anniversary Home" for Robin Aire Development Co. and related work (2 of 2)
    - (3 of 4)., 1955 (Folder 228)
      - M. Wiesberg., 1955.; 22 items.
        Job Number 55-58. Tract No. 21978 for M. Wiesberg.
        20 homes.
        San Fernando Mission Blvd at Woodley Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Meyer Wiesberg.
    - (4 of 4)., 1955 (Folder 229)
      - Raygard Corp., 1955.; 11 items.
        Job Number 55-65. Tract No. 19001 for Raygard Corp.
        6 homes. Collett Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Raygard Corp.
    - (1 of 5)., 1956 (Folder 230)
      - Los Angeles Home Show., 1956.; 1.; 4 items.
        Cinderella's Dream Home for Los Angeles Home Show
        Original and copy of drawings: plan, elevations, perspectives.
      - Mr. & Mrs. Horsburgh., 1956.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 56-4. Anniversary Homes revised for Mr. & Mrs. Horsburgh
        Mt. Vernon Dr. View Park, Los Angeles County, CA.
      - Chathurst Worthmore Corp., 1956.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 56-6. Residence for Chathurst Worthmore Corp.
        Owner: Chathurst Worthmore Corp.
    - (2 of 5)., 1956 (Folder 231)
      - Traub Co., 1956.; 1.; 8 items.
        Job Number 56-8. Residence for the Traub Co.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Leon Traub.
      - Mr. Sam Sheiner., 1956.; 2.; 20 items.
        Job Number 56-34. Tract No. 22505 for Mr. Sam Sheiner
        6 homes. Rinaldi St.
        Owner: Mr. Sam Sheiner.
    - (3 of 5)., 1956 (Folder 232)
      - Tem Construction Co., 1956.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 56-36. Residence for Tem Construction Co.
        19324 Romar St. Chatsworth, CA.
        Owner: Tem Construction Co.
      - Mesa Manor Inc., 1956.; 2.; 17 items.
        Job Number 56-40. Tract No. 2947 for Mesa Manor Inc.
        42 homes. Raleigh Ave. Costa Mesa, CA.
        Owner: Mesa Manor Inc.
    - (4 of 5)., 1956 (Folder 233)
      - Traub Co., 1956.; 31 items.
        Job Number 56-53. Residence for the Traub Co.
        Country Club Dr. Glendale, CA.
    - (5 of 5)., 1956 (Folder 234)
      - Capri Developments Inc., 1956.; 5 items.
        Job Number 56-58. Residence for the Capri Developments Inc.
        Owner: Capri Developments Inc.
    - (1 of 3)., 1957 (Folder 235)
      - Waverly Heights., 1957.; 1.; 15 items.
        Job Number 57-10. Model Home no. 1-3 for Waverly Heights
        Ventura County, CA. Lots 8, 15.
      - F. Monelllo Co., 1957.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 57-26. Residence for F. Monelllo Co.
        Atoll St. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: F. Monelllo Co.
      - Joseph Mullender., 1957.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 57-28. Residence for Joseph Mullender
        7 homes.
        Workman Ave. & Idahome St. West Covina, CA.
        Owner: Joseph Mullender.
    - (2 of 3)., 1957 (Folder 236)
      - Capri Developments Inc., 1957.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 57-32. Residence for the Capri Developments Inc.
      - Capri Developments Inc., 1957.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 57-35. Residence for the Capri Developments Inc.
        5011 Palomar Dr. Tarzana, CA.
    - (3 of 3)., 1957 (Folder 237)
      - Capri Developments Inc., 1957.; 1.; 7 items.
        Job Number 57-45. Residence for the Capri Developments Inc.
        Palomar Dr. Tarzana, CA.
      - Atlas Development Co., 1957.; 2.; 8 items.
        Job Number 57-46. Residence for the Atlas Development Co.
        15427 Milldale Rd. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Ralph H. Winkler.
    - ., 1958-1959 (Folder 238)
      - Cemex Cabin., 1958.; 1.; 2 items.
        Cemex Cabin
      - Roy Schuch., 1959.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 59-10. Residence for the Roy Schuch
        Owner: Roy Schuch.
      - Vogue Development Co., 1959.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 59-30. Residence for the Vogue Development Co.
        3331 Longridge Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Vogue Development Co.
      - Vogue Development Co., 1959.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 59-31. Residence for the Vogue Development Co.
        3347 Longridge Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
      - Vogue Development Co., 1959.; 5.; 4 items.
        Job Number 59-32. Residence for the Vogue Development Co.
        3276 Longridge Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
    - ., 1960 (Folder 239)
      - Vogue Development Co., 1960.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 60-3. Residence for the Vogue Development Co.
        Longridge Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
      - Vogue Development Co., 1960.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 60-4. Residence for the Vogue Development Co.
        3277 Longridge Terrace, Sherman Oaks, CA.
      - Harvey Knox., 1960.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 60-23. Duplex for Harvey Knox
        42100 Pacific Coast Highway, Solimar CA.
      - Haas Development Co., 1960.; 4.; 6 items.
        Job Number 60-30. Residence for Haas Development Co.
        Original drawings: plans, section, details and elevations.
        Owner: Haas Development Co.
    - (1 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 240)
      - Haas Development Co., 1961.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 61-5. Residence for Haas Development Co.
        5816 Winnetka Ave. Woodland Hills, CA.
      - The Cemex Moresque Model Home, Cemex Homesteader., 1961.; 2.; 15 items.
        Job Numbers 61-8, 61-24, 61-27. The Cemex Moresque Model Home, Cemex Homesteader and related work
        Apple Valley, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, details, elevations and perspectives.
        Owner: Cemex.
    - (2 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 241)
      - Haas Development Co., 1961.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 61-16. Residence for Haas Development Co.
        16588 Calneva Dr. Encino, CA.
      - Lorelei Construction Co., 1961.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 61-20. Residence for Lorelei Construction Co.
        15577 High Knoll Rd. Royal Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Lorelei Construction Co.
      - "Homes by Haas"., 1961.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 61-22. Residence for "Homes by Haas"
        5836 Winnetka Ave. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Original drawing: plan and section.
      - Harvey Knox., 1961.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 61-49. Duplex for Harvey Knox
      - Harvey Knox., 1961.; 5.; 5 items.
        Job Number 61-50. Duplex for Harvey Knox
    - ., 1962-1964 (Folder 242)
      - Cannell & Chaffin., 1962.; 1.; 2 items.
        Residence for Cannell & Chaffin
        Owner: Cannell & Chaffin Inc.
      - Columbia Properties., 1964.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 64-14. Residence for Columbia Properties
        18770 Edeleen St. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Columbia Properties Inc.
- Series 6: Bids and forms., ca. 1940-1960; 1 boxes.
  - Bids and forms., ca. 1940-1960. (Box 243)
    Box of description of materials forms for Ayres & Fiege homes, and bid forms for assorted military housing installments, airports, etc. for a construction contractor named Harry Hart.